

## Contact



06 13 03 25 25

78550 Houdan



celia.martinelli2@gmail.com



www.linkedin.com/in/celiamartinelli



https://github.com/celiamartinelli



https://celia-martinelli.netlify.app/

### **SOFT SKILLS**

- Adaptability
- Motivation
- Time Management
- Self-Discipline
- Problem Solving
- Curiosity
- Organized
- Communication Skills

### **HARD SKILLS**

### **Front-End**

ReactJS / Redux / JavaScript /
React Native / TypeScript / Next.js

#### **Back-End**

Nodejs / PostgresSQL / Sequelize / ExpressJS / Strapi (cms) / Supabase

### Web Intégration

HTML5 / CSS3 / Sass / Tailwind / Material UI / Sematic UI

**Project Management**GitHub / Notion / Whimsical /

Expo / Figma / Canva /

### **HOBBIES**



Animal Welfare - Treasurer of the association - The Houdanais Country Cat School since 01/04/2024

Aromatherapy - Health - Wellbeing Making cosmetics

Self-taught sewing

# **CÉLIA** MARTINELLI

# WEB DÉVELOPPEUSE

### Specialized: Javascript, React, React Native

A web developer passionate about UI/UX, I invest myself carefully in every detail to offer intuitive and aesthetic interfaces. My keen sense of detail and my creativity allow me to transform ideas into harmonious and engaging user experiences. Ready to bring my expertise to ambitious projects, I am motivated by innovation and the constant search for quality.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### WEB DEVELOPER - IOS & ANDROID APPLICATION

**Start Up Yuli** - Front and back web development internship 03-2024 à 08-2024

- Team development of an IOS and Android application, from its design to its deployment, specializing in animal welfare.
- Technologies: React Native, Expo, Redux, Supabase, Google API, Apple API

### WEB DEVELOPER - END OF TRAINING PROJECT

O'clock School - End of training project

01-2024 à 02-2024

 Creation of a web application as a team, from its design to the deployment of an MVP in agile methodology.
 HERE

#### ADVISOR AND FLORIST IN GARDEN CENTER

Poullain Garden Center - CDI - la Queue lez Yvelines (78)

2018 - 2022

- Communication, identification of needs, taking initiative, versatility
- Preparation of bouquets and floral arrangements
- Administrative management of the cash desk: Organization, problem solving, adaptability

#### DIGITAL RETOUCHER

**Showroomprivé.com** - CDI - Saint-Denis - Lille - Roubaix 2018 - 2013

- Team management: information sharing, active listening, teaching, organizational skills
- Retouching: Artistic sensitivity, attention to detail, rigor, patience

#### LB Production (Louis Vuitton) FREE LANCE

Paris - 2013 - 2012

Retouching: Precision, self-discipline, time management

### EDUCATION

WEB AND MOBILE WEB DEVELOPER TRAINING -

O'CLOCK SCHOOL Sep 2023 - Feb 2024

Professional Title Level V - Remote Training - 798 intensive hours

# TRAINING IN PHOTOGRAPHY AND COMMUNICATION PROFESSIONS - EFET PHOTOGRAPHIE 2010 - 2012

- CFE End of year diploma Photo Book Graphic charter Website Project exhibition
- Professional Baccalaureate in Photography
- CAP in Photography at School